# Miranda Montez

New York, NY 10028 | 218-390-3779 | monte141@uw.edu

#### SUMMARY

Versatile professional in pursuit of MLIS degree with four years of experience working in a library seeking to bring a fresh perspective to a new library position. Background includes performing all tasks associated with circulation and interlibrary loan. Accustomed to managing data and working with databases. Extremely organized, efficient, and detail-oriented.

#### EXPERIENCE

WHITNEY MUSEUM OF AMERICAN ART, NEW YORK, NY

January 2018-Present

# **Library Intern**

- Perform circulation tasks, such as mail, checking books in and out, and customer service.
- Create and organize MARC Records for files and books.
- Utilize Voyageur Circulation and Cataloging Databases.

DR. CORRIE HORSHINSKI, D.C., CHIROPRACTOR, NEW YORK, NY

November 2016 - Present

### Receptionist

Provide administrative assistance and manage HIPAA-compliant customer relations.

St. Louis County Public Health and Human Services, Duluth, MN

May 2015 – June 2016

### **Information Specialist I**

- Entered customer information into databases (Compass Pilot, Compass Appointments, OnBase, RightFax, Maxis, and Curam).
- Received and processed all incoming phone calls, mail, and faxes.

KATHRYN A. MARTIN LIBRARY, Duluth, MN

August 2011 – May 2015

# Interlibrary Loan Specialist – Lead, Circulation Staff

- Utilized databases, including Alma, ILLiad, Ariel, and Aleph, to complete circulation processes such as checking in and out materials.
- Managed the opening and closing of the building and supervised several student workers as they checked in/out materials, interacted with patrons, and organized books.

Wal-Mart, Hermantown, MN

June 2012 - May 2015

#### Cashier

# **E**DUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF WASHINGTON

September 2017 - May 2020 (expected)

# **Master of Library and Information Science**

University of Minnesota — Duluth

May 2015

# **Bachelor of Arts in Political Science and International Studies**

GPA: 3.86/4.0

Study Abroad Academic Year: University of Worcester, Worcester, England

### ADDITIONAL EXPERIENCE

SETON HALL UNIVERSITY, South Orange, NJ

July 2014

# United Nations (UN) Intensive Summer Study Program, School of Diplomacy and International Relations

# LANGUAGE AND COMPUTER SKILLS

Word Spanish (limited working proficiency) Microsoft Windows Excel English (native) Apple OSX/macOS

PowerPoint Typing speed of 68 WPM Scan, fax and copy machine experience